http://www.forplaycatalog.com/privacy-policy

Privacy and Security
Forplay Catalog collects client information to make your online shopping experience the best on the Internet. We respect your privacy, and assure you that we will maintain and use this information responsibly.
General Browsing
ForplayCatalog.com gathers navigational information about where you go on our Web site. This information allows us to see which areas of ForplayCatalog.com are most visited. This helps us improve the quality of visitors' online shopping experiences by recognizing and delivering more of the features, services and products our visitors prefer. Additional non-personally identifiable information (i.e. domain type, browser version, service provider and IP address) may be collected which will provide information regarding your use of our Web site (such as the time of your last visit to a page on our site).
Disclosure of Personal Information
Any information you provide to us at this site when you establish an account, shop online or request information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card information), is maintained in private files on our secure Web server and our internal systems. This information is used to enable ForplayCatalog.com to deliver services to you. To ensure compliance with federal law, Forplay Catalog does not maintain information provided by children under the age of 18.
Your orders placed through ForplayCatalog.com will be accepted and fully processed in and shipped from the U.S. and all information you provide will be processed and securely maintained in our Web server and internal systems located within the U.S.
You should be aware that we may disclose specific information about you if necessary to do so by law or based on our good faith belief that it is necessary to conform or comply with the law or is necessary to protect the users of our Web site, the site or the public.
Forplay Catalog does not sell or rent your e-mail address to third parties. We may, however, use third parties to help us provide services to you, such as fulfilling orders, processing payments, monitoring site activity, conducting surveys, and administering e-mails, drawings or contests. If personally identifiable information (i.e. name, address, e-mail address, telephone number) is provided to any of these third parties, we will require that such information be maintained by them in strictest confidence.
If you purchase merchandise through ForplayCatalog.com, your name and mailing address will be added to the Forplay Catalog print Catalog mailing list and database.
Use of Cookies
Forplay Catalog uses a browser feature known as a cookie, which assigns a unique identification to your computer. Cookies also allow Forplay Catalog to make our site more responsive to your needs, by delivering a better and more personalized experience to you. The cookies are typically stored on your computer's hard drive and are used by Forplay Catalog to help track your clicks as you go through the pages within Forplay Catalog Web site. In addition, Forplay Catalog uses cookies to help keep track of items you put into your shopping bag and to tell us whether you have previously visited ForplayCatalog.com. This allows registered users to avoid reentering information upon every new visit to our site. If you register or purchase product through ForplayCatalog.com, navigational information from previous browsing visits may be associated with the personal information you provide.
Forplay Catalog E-mail
Forplay Catalog E-Mail allows you to receive exclusive information about special offers, media events, new products and much more. If you're not already registered, simply complete our sign up form to receive these special messages. If at any time you would like to stop future delivery of Forplay Catalog E-Mail, please follow the removal instructions located at the bottom of each message or complete the removal from e-mail form. Asking to be removed from Forplay Catalog E-Mail will not prevent you from receiving e-mail confirmations for any order you place at ForplayCatalog.com.
Questions/Changes in Policy
If you have questions or concerns with respect to our Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us. If elements of our Privacy Policy change, we will post the policy changes in our Privacy Policy on this Web site. If you are concerned about how your personal information is used, please visit our site often for this and other important announcements about Forplay Catalog.
QUICK LINKS
BLOG
FAQ'S
PRIVACY POLICY
SIZE CHARTS
TERMS & CONDITIONS
WANNA COLLAB?
Also notify me about New Arrivals!
Providing the highest quality Hollywood-style apparel to the rest of the world!
Lingerie
